Chime
We'll be right back.
There, that should do it.
I love when you cook for your father and I on Saturdays so I can relax.
Yum! Delicious!
Unfortunately, my first experience of going to eat ramen with friends turned out to be a dud.
Crap, I forgot! But I was so ready to eat some ramen!
Naturally, Yoshida was the most disappointed out of all three of us.
Low-sodium ramen is garbage! Like, get out of here with that stuff!
We went and got tea instead.
Yano and I listened as Yoshida talked about ramen.
It was so fun!
My friends are so cool!
Oh, you're making curry today, Sawako?
Huh?
Uh, so today's curry, huh?
I'll answer it.
Yes, this is Kuro-Numa.
Guess I'm being ignored.
It's for Sawako!
It's somebody saying they're a friend of yours!
Hey, Sawako! Get ready, cause ramen's on the menu tonight!
Ramen's on the menu?
Hmph! So, let's get our revenge!
My friends are inviting me to get ramen! Can I please go?
Friends of yours?
Of course you can! Now hurry and go meet with them!
But I haven't started serving the curry yet!
Oh, don't you worry! I'll take care of it!
Make sure you bring them over sometime, Sawako!
Okay!
Our little girl is going out with friends!
She did mention that she's been having fun lately.
That reminds me about the other day when she came home later than she usually does.
Now wait a minute! Are these friends boys or girls?
No idea!
Oh! You're here!
Today I finally get to eat ramen with my friends!
By the way, Sawako, I don't think either of us ever asked you for your cell phone number.
What is it?
I don't have one.
Wait, is that true?
Yeah. I've just never felt the need to bother with one, I guess.
Ah, that makes sense.
Well, if you ever get the urge to buy one, then let us know.
Welcome!
Come on in, Jizu!
You brought some friends with you today?
Heck yeah! Now hook us up, Pops!
Heh heh heh heh! Can't say no to a request from you, miso!
I wanted you to try this ramen no matter what it took!
It's the best!
I'll just take the usual!
You got it!
What are you getting? I recommend some miso!
Oh, I'll get that then.
I'll take a shoyu, please.
Was my recommendation not good enough?
I've had it before.
Look! There's no water in here!
I'm sorry for the wait.
Change it before someone notices!
My dad.
I thought I saw Sanada just now.
No, you're right. It's him.
Uh-huh. He lives right upstairs from here.
Really?
Okay. Miso ramen for you.
Looks awesome, right?
Thanks a lot for the meal!
Man, I'm stuffed.
Pops really does make the best ramen in town.
Yes, thanks.
And it was twice as delicious because I ate it with the two of you.
Thanks. We're gonna head upstairs now.
Sure. Make yourselves comfortable.
Wait, what?
Come on in, guys.
Interesting. Did you move in here?
Huh? No? Why?
So, um, can I come along too?
Yeah, of course you can.
You're real silly, you know that?
I've never noticed it before,
but Yoshida and Sanada must be close.
Get comfy. There's plenty of room in here.
Sorry. Give me a second.
Oh, hello.
Uh-huh.
So popular.
What, right now?
Huh?
Uh, sorry, but I'm hanging out with friends today,
so I can't go with you.
Huh?
They're both girls.
Go on, say something.
M-Miso ramen is so-
You see?
Yeah, okay. I'll message you when I'm done.
Later.
Boyfriend?
Uh, yeah, it was.
She has one?
Isn't your current guy in university?
You don't need to say current.
Wow, you're so grown up, Yano.
Ugh, don't you worry.
You'll reach the magnificent world of being a grown up too,
and it'll happen before you know it.
You really think so?
Chizu, same goes for you.
Ugh, you're always saying grown up this, grown up that,
but can you defeat 99 dudes in a row?
Right.
That weird record you keep of your consecutive wins in middle school.
Weird?
What the heck do you even know, you uncultured idiot?
I've kind of been wondering why it's only 99.
Who was your 100th opponent?
Ryu.
Whoa, congrats on preventing your 100th straight win, Ryu.
Why are you here?
You can't just show up unannounced!
This is my room, though.
Um, by any chance...
Hmm?
Are you...
Are you two dating each other?
I knew it.
No way!
It's a yes or no question, so you should pick one, Ryu.
Uh-huh.
Don't confirm something when it's not true!
I suppose me and Shizuru are more like brothers than anything else.
Hold up! Who's the older brother and who's the younger one?
That's your biggest concern about this.
Oh, I see.
Huh?
I don't have any siblings, so I'm totally envious.
Not you too, Sadako.
Laughter.
An exuberant place.
Friends who I truly love.
Staying by their side.
It really is okay, isn't it?
Hey, should we call of Kaze Haya while we're here?
K-Call Kaze Haya?
Can't let Ryu be the only one allowed to enjoy the harem, right?
The what?
Well, I imagine it's tough being the lone guy in a room.
Ryu, cell phone.
You call him, Sadako.
Here.
Wait, me?
Uh-huh.
Are you sure that's okay?
Why wouldn't it be?
Come on, just call him already.
Kaze Haya's gonna pick up thinking it's Ryu and be super shocked when he hears a girl's voice.
Press the phone button to start calling.
My heart is racing.
There's nothing to be so nervous about.
Kaze Haya's definitely gonna be the one to pick up.
He is?
Now my heart's racing even more.
Say, we're having fun.
Hurry over.
Or Ryu's outnumbered by girls.
Save him.
Well...
I'd like him to be here.
Hmm?
A phone call!
Who is it, huh, Shota?
Tell me!
Oh, that's Ryu.
Giddy!
I want to talk to him, too!
Chill out.
No!
Hey, come on!
Stop it!
Is this Kaze Haya?
It's Kuro Numa.
Ryu!
Can you hear me?
I want to talk!
Wait, what do you mean this is?
But isn't this the number for...
How come...
What's going on?
So, I met Sanada's and...
Ryu's house?
Iyano Yoshida and I went to get ramen today.
So that's why I'm with them all right now.
Okay.
I...
I'm really having a lot of fun.
Being with everyone makes things more enjoyable.
And if you were here, too,
we thought it'd be even more fun than it already is.
I'll zip over on my bike.
He's on his way!
Now!
I'll say hi, huh?
You were...
having that much fun with us?
And that's me!
Ah!
You three have really been in the same class
ever since you were in middle school?
For second and third year.
Hmm, Ryu and Kaze Haya are...
He hasn't changed even a bit.
Hmm, for as long as I can remember,
he's always looked exactly the same.
But I've gotten so much taller.
Whoa!
This must be Kaze Haya's middle school photo.
So this must be everyone's Kaze Haya, huh?
Too baby-faced for me.
His hair!
Ah, he was growing it out then.
It was after shaving his head for baseball season.
But Ryu's always had a buzz cut, regardless of playing sports.
Cause it's easy.
That's the kind of guy he is.
Shota's a great baseball player.
When he didn't join our high school team,
Kane was pretty disappointed.
A side of Kaze Haya that I was unaware of.
I wonder what he was like in middle school.
Was he someone who studied earnestly?
And got in as much practice as he could?
I wish I could have seen him play.
Oh, you probably can.
Our field day is coming up fairly soon.
I bet Kaze Haya will join the softball team.
Is that true?
I can watch Kaze Haya in the present going forward.
Not to mention, I can be in the pictures with everyone.
And be invited to do so many things with them.
There's field day, school trips, and a whole lot more.
I'm really excited.
I'm excited for everything.
You'll have fun.
I know it.
And you'll eat tons of good food, too.
Now that I have friends,
I can share the same joys with all of them.
Oh, this girl is...
Huh?
That's Kurumi.
How do you know her?
She helped me pick up some handouts
that I dropped in the hallway once.
What's that face you're making, Chizu?
Uh, it's nothing.
Looks like the kind to be popular with the guys.
Yep, that's her.
Ryo, look.
What's your verdict?
She's not my type.
Whoa, I didn't think you actually had a type.
Okay, then what about this one here?
I like her fine.
Well, I like you fine also, Sanada.
And what about the two of us?
I... I love you.
So that's what you mean.
You kind of had us worried for a second.
All right, Sadako.
What do you think of Kazuhaya?
Oh!
I...
Yen...
love...
you...
Yanuji, by love, does she mean the same way she feels about us?
Oh, definitely not.
Then does she realize she's got feelings for him?
No, I'm thinking that she doesn't.
Sarako, that means you...
Please, Shizu, no need to rush the girl into anything.
Sometimes you've got to climb the stairs of adulthood step by step all alone.
How in the hell do you make a simple thing like that sound so dirty?
I'm back!
Pops, one miso.
One miso coming right up.
Phew, close one.
That could have been a bad situation.
I'm coming upstairs!
Wait, Kasehaya's hair?
I just noticed it's pretty long compared to the other players, isn't it?
Yeah, his seems to grow a lot faster than most people's.
It kind of makes him look like a perv.
What if he secretly is one?
Even if I was a perv, it wouldn't be a secret!
You freaking scared me.
You really burst in here with that creepy comment?
What?
I'm normal.
I swear.
I'm supposed to take that seriously?
You may as well have said I'm a total pervert.
I said I'm normal.
He's such a boy, isn't he?
Hey, look! Sarako's so laughing at you, Kasehaya!
Kuro Numa?
It's already embarrassing enough!
No, I wasn't trying to make fun of you or anything!
I promised!
In fact…
Kidding.
Feel free to laugh.
For some reason, it feels like my heart's beating faster.
Is it because I'm closer to him here than our seats in the classroom?
Hmm…
Sadako, I mean Sawako…
Why don't you come over here and sit right next to Chizu and me?
K…
Oh? You're really moving?
Come on, don't be shy.
K…
Tonight's been lots of fun, hasn't it?
Yeah!
Wow, Sawako, you smell so nice!
Is that a new lotion?
I love it!
This is too good.
Prince Charming is over there suffering.
I've discovered my new source of entertainment!
And…
Playtime's over, everybody out!
Bean!
Go home, you scumbag!
Maybe you should go home since it's way past your bedtime!
What is Mr. Arai doing here?
Did we get reported for being too loud?
No, Kuronuma, it's not that.
Ha!
In my early days, I used to be in the little league baseball team this guy's dad coached.
So I've known him since he was a tiny brat!
Plus he's a regular here and he's about as rude as rude can be.
Is that really true?
Guess you wouldn't know that, huh?
Hold on! Are you guys not seeing this at all?
There!
When I stared into her eyes, I saw reflections of a bunch of little old men!
Peen!
Um…
If you're seeing little old men, there's one at my house.
I…
I knew it!
Hey, Peen, have you ever gotten sleep paralysis?
Yeah!
I got it all the time when I was a kid.
I still get it pretty often, though.
When it happens, do you hear any weird noises in your room by chance?
Uh-huh!
But mostly in my sleep.
You know, things like creak, zap, boom…
Doesn't that mean you might have a sixth sense or something?
Now that you mention it, there was this heaviness.
And that must be the reason that I didn't get much sleep last night.
Excuse me?
I'd suggest putting some salt in a bath and soaking in it to help you sleep better.
Purifying salt?
It will warm your body up and let you sleep peacefully.
Is this kid some kind of exorcist?
I hope that helped.
Do your best.
Hey, that's enough, get out of here!
Twerp!
Why don't you go home?
It's gonna be nine o'clock soon.
These two are so stupid!
Who knew we'd get a show?
Shut it!
Now get going or else!
Hey, we should start heading out, too.
Another side of him I get to see!
Tonight was so much fun!
It was, wasn't it?
And from now on, we're gonna have fun together like this all the time, Sarako!
I got to spend Saturday night with my friends.
Thank you for having us!
It was a moment in time that I couldn't believe I had experienced.
Hey, I have to hit the store so let's walk together.
My heart is racing, but it feels comforting.
Hey, get her home, Mr. Gentlemen!
We're counting on you, Mr. Gentlemen!
I seriously hate them.
Everyone was smiling, and it made me really happy.
We're gonna have fun together like this all the time, Sarako!
See you later, Chizu.
Yeah, good night, Yanochin.
Why are you going the same way I'm going?
You're acting like I have a choice!
You're troubled! Don't stand so close!
Listen! I can't be alone in the dark!
All right, then. Guess I should leave.
I could go home and take a bath.
Oh, that's right!
You never did tell us what your type is, Ryu!
Yeah, and?
Come on, man! Kurumi's not your type, so I wanna know who is!
I guess... someone who's dense and straightforward.
That is some interesting taste you have.
Well, yeah.
Dense and straightforward?
Is it someone like Sarako after all?
You know, you really didn't have to bother.
Because I'm already aware.
Uh, about what exactly?
You came to tell me, didn't you?
That you finally made up with her.
Uh...
My heart is still racing.
And it seems like it might stay like this forever.
I really enjoyed tonight.
I'm glad... that I ended up coming to this high school.
Uh...
And it's nice being able to be in the same classes with everyone.
Am...
I included in there, too?
Uh...
Of course!
Kazuhaya, if it wasn't for you, then...
My life would've been way different!
You're giving me too much credit.
Uh...
Sorry.
I've just been a little sulky.
Uh...
You were?
To be honest, all I wanted was some reassurance.
I'm seeing things in his face that I've never seen before.
Expressions that are totally new to me.
They make me feel like...
I'm getting a peek at parts of him I didn't know about.
My heart is so full.
about. My heart is so full. Hey, Kazuhaya, what were you gonna buy at the store?
Hmm, that's a really good question. Huh? What? I hope I can see more new sides of him in the future.
Mr. Latte film Visit our website at MarEven.com
Yeah!
Oh fuck.
Remember ...
Also, the students on theziehend перекrit,
these days, they will take many things to watch early.
I'll make their fault now.
Me, Amazon, and my friend 쓰는omi va dot com
It's not a dream
I want to know
I want to see
Just a moment
But
I want to see
The sky is a
This is a dream
I want to see
Just a moment
The sky is a
You
It's not a dream
I want to see
The sky is a dream
And a dream
It's a dream
But
At the sky is a dream
The sky is a dream
The sky is the dream
It's a dream
There's a dream